# Daniel Gawne

## **Full Stack Developer**

danielgawne@gmail.com dgawne.com

386-848-9757

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dgwne/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/dgwne/</a>

GitHub: https://github.com/dgwn

## Skills

I am experienced in JavaScript, HTML, CSS/Sass, ReactJS, Git, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, PSQL, Typescript, Linux Server Admin, Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, and XD. I have also worked with Python, R, and Ruby. I am a self-taught programmer which demonstrates my dedication to continued and self-directed learning.

#### **Experience**

### Raterlabs, Inc. / Senior Internet Analyst

JUNE 2017 - PRESENT, Remote

Conduct research, evaluation and feedback on search engine results by, but not limited to: measuring the relevance and usefulness of web pages in correlation to predefined queries, by providing comparative analysis of sets of search engine results and various other techniques. Evaluate and improve search engine results for some of the world's largest internet search engine companies. Consistently meets high quality standards on monthly reviews and performs in the top 10% of employees.

#### Fleet Farming / Digital Media/Marketing Intern

JAN 2018 - MAY 2018, Orlando, FL

Developed targeted Facebook ad campaigns for selected demographics, wrote original ad copy, managed Facebook and Instagram feeds, calculated effectiveness of ad spending on sales and brand awareness, monitored Google Analytics for our website, monitored and selected keywords using Google AdWords, drafted and designed promotional materials for both print and web (e.g. fliers, calendar, infographics, and stickers), and developed action plans for future interns in the Media/Marketing department.

#### **Leapforce / Search Engine Evaluator**

SEPT 2015 - MAY 2017, Remote

Conducted in depth internet-based research and provided information evaluation for leading search and social media companies from around the globe.

#### **Education**

University of Central Florida/ Philosophy B.A. (Sociology Minor) 2012 - 2017, Orlando, FL

**University of Helsinki/** Full Stack Open - Web Dev Coursework 2022

Full Stack Open - Course Completion (University of Helsinki)

 $Responsive\ Web\ Design,\ Javascript\ Algorithms\ \&\ Data\ Structures\ \ (FreeCodeCamp)$ 

Adobe Certified Associate (Photoshop & InDesign CS5)

### Certifications